Guide to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V. Office of the Far Eastern Affairs
  - Subseries V.3: Administrative Branch. Country File
    - Far East Personnel (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - India Recruitment (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 224/11 India Recruitment (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 021/250 India Rundown 021/25B (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 021/25B Korea Rundown 021/25E (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 022/21 Philippines Teletype Manila (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 024/25F Philippines Rundown (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - SWPAO (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Candidates (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Sidney Office (General Correspondence) (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 403/3 Personnel Vol. II (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 244/14 Recruitment (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 021/250 Rundown (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
  - Subseries V.4: Analysis Branch. Country File
    - 083/1D Australia and New Guinea, Population and Social Conditions (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Burma (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 077/60 Health and Welfare (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - China (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Agencies with which United China Relief Has Dealings (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/82A Private Agencies (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/82A Private Agencies File #2 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 171/82 Surveys & Appreciations by Outside Agencies (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Agriculture (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Business vs UNRRA (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/50 Commerce, Domestic and Foreign (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/33 Communications (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/32A Cotton (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/310 Rural Credit (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Public Criticism (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Delegates to UNRRA Atlantic City Conference (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 702/2 Directive (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Displaced Persons (incl. Japanese) (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 708/1H Distribution (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Economic Resources & Industries File #1, 1943-5 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - Economic Resources & Industries File #2, 1946 - (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/11 Education (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/31G Fertilizer (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/40 Government Finance & Banking (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/44 Financial Problems of Relief and Rehabilitation (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/31 Food & Agriculture upto & incl. 1943, File #1 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/31 Food & Agriculture 1944 File #2 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 1)
    - China (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Food & Agriculture 1945, File #3 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/31 Food & Agriculture 1946, File #4 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/52 Foreign Trade Regulations (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/34 Fuel & Electricity (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - General (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/90 General incl. Bibliography (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/20 Government (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/60 Health and Welfare (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/51 Import & Export (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - I.R. Projects (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - I.W.T. (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/35 Extractive Industries (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Industrialization (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/31E Insecticides (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 752/1 Letters Commencing with Monthly Report #1 for Dec. 1945 (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Letters to and from OFE (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/31L Livestock (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/3IF Machinery (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 703/2 Organization & Staff (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/10 Population & Social Conditions (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/37C Ports (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Program Agriculture (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 712/2 "Beachhead" Emergency Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Clothing Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - 712 Emergency Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - DP (Displaced Persons) Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Flooded Areas Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Food Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - General Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Health & Medical Care Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Industries Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - I.R. Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - Misc. Program (Box FE/6, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 712/3 Ports Emergency Program (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Relief Program (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 714/1 2nd Six Months Program (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Shelter (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Six Months Program General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Transport & Communications (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Welfare (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/39 Regional Studies (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Amoy Foochow Areas, Fukien Areas, Chekiang Areas (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/39 Central China, Chekiang File #2 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Fukien (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/39A North China (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/39C South China File #1 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/39C South China File #2 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - South China (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Relief Material (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Relief and Rehabilitation (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/80 Relief & Rehabilitation (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 087/2 Requirements (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 087/1 Requirements (Requirements Estimates Submitted at Atlantic City) (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/31A Rice (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/37A Roads (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 721/25A Rundown (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/33 Shelter (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Supplies for Communist Areas from UNRRA Program (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/82 Survey & Appreciations by Outside Agencies (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/32 Textiles, Clothing & Accessories (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Farm Tractor Operations (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Tractor Relief Plowing & Training Project (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Air China Transport (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/27 Transportation Facilities up to & incl. 1945 #1 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Transportation Facilities 1946 File #2 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - United China Relief (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/36 Waterways Conservation (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Other Waterworks (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/31K Veterinary Services (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/31B Wheat (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/36B Yellow River (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/311 Yellow River Project (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/51 CNRRA & UNRRA Developments (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Far East (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Bibliography (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Food Tables and Trade in Agricultural Products (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 086/10 Populations & Social Conditions (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Health (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Relief & Rehabilitation General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 087/1 Requirement General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 071/39E Formosa Regional Studies (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Hong Kong (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 702/4 India Office Directive (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - India General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Indochina Economy (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 075/60 Indochina Health & Welfare (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 075/80 Indochina Relief & Rehabilitation (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 075/80 Indochina Relief & Rehabilitation (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - 87/5 Indochina Requirements (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Japan, Analysis & Intelligence (Box FE/7, Folder Side 1)
    - Japan (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 073/50 Japan Commerce, Domestic & Foreign (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 073/30 Economic Resources & Industry (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Exports of Textiles (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Pending File (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Korea (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 716/1 Correspondence & Cables (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Confidential (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Directive (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Finance (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 256/7 Special Missions - Gaines (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Malaya (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Manchuria General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 071/39D Mancuria Regional Studies (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Netherlands East Indies (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Advance Purchase for (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Relief Program (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Requirements Combined Boards (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Spectifcations Part I (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Specifications Part II, Vol. I (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Specifications Part II, Vol. II (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Agricultural Products (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 080/30 Economic Resources & Industry (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Foodstuffs (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 080/90 General Bibliography (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 080/60 Health & Welfare (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Imports & Exports (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Industrialization (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Population (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 080/2 Relief & Rehabilitation (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Philippines (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 753/17 Agricultural Rehabilitation 1945 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 752/4 General Dispatches (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Farm Machinery & Equipment Requirements (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 074/31 Food & Agriculture (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Food Requirements (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - General 1944-5 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 753/15 Health 1945 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 753/16 Industrial Rehabilitation 1945 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 074/10 Populations & Social Conditions (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 755/19 Public Information (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Request for $102,000,000 18 August 1945 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Requirements (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 753/16 Welfare 1945 (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Siam (Thailand) (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - General (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 076/00 Siam Geography (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 076/60 Siam & Welfare (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Requirements (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - SWPAO (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - 702/3 Directive (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Dispatches (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - Sidney Dispatches Accounting (Box FE/7, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241 DPs (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241/3/E DP Budget January 1947 Vol. II (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241/1 DPs General (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241/3B DPs Feeding (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241/5 China Koreans Displaced (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 045/9 20 Chinese Nurses (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241/6 Overseas Chinese (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel & Training Letters from (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 241/4 Rabbinical Students (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - Rabbinical Students for Canada (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - Rabbinical Students for Europe & ME (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 246/6 Remittances for V.A. in Shanghai (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 514/1 2nd Six Months Program (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 514/1 2nd Six Months Program (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 514/1 2nd Six Months Program (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - 514 2nd Six Months Program (Box FE/8, Folder Side 1)
    - China (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 245/6 50 Chinese Trainees (Technical Experts) in U.S. Vol. I (January - September 1944) (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 245/6 50 Chinese Trainess (Technical Experts) in U.S. Vol. II (October - December 1944) (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 245/6 50 Chinese Trainees (Technical Experts) in U.S. Vol. III (January 1945- June 1946) 245/6 50 Chinese Trainees (Technical Experts) in U.S. Vol. IV (July - December 1946) 245/6 50 Chinese Trainees (Technical Experts) in U.S. Vol. V (from January 1947) (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - Training Recruits (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - Transportation (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 244/7 Welfare Programs of Other Agencies (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 244/1 Committee on Chinese Personnel for CNRRA (80 Chinese Recruited by CNRRA in USA for Welfare Work in China) (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - Europe, Chinese DPs (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - Far East, DPs in India, Burma, Malaya (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 252/5 DPs in New Britain (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - Formosa (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 242/4 Indochina DPs in Indochina (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 242/7 Japan, DPs in (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 042/10 Netherlands East Indies (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 242/2 Philippine DPs in Manila (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 242/6 Siam, DPs in (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - 246/7 SWPAO V.A. Sydney Group (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - Thailand Legation, Visit of Dr. O'Brien & Glen Briggs (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
  - Subseries V.5: Program Branch. Country File
    - 039/2 Procurement Australia (Box FE/8, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 036 Agricultural Rehabilitation Fisheries (FRA) Jan. 1946-Sept.1947 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 036 FRA Vol. II Oct. 1947 Shanghai (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 234/1A Problems of Medical Reflie & Rehabilitation, Reports by Chinese Delegation to UNRRA (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 233/2 Shelter Requirements 038/6 Kowloon, Shipping Arrangement in (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/5 Surprop (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 229/5 Sruprop (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/5 Surprop, Oct. 1945- Sept.1947 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/5 Surprop, Oct. 1947 Vol. II (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 035 Transportation (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 035/6 China Inland Water Transport (Shanghai) Vol. I 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 035/6 China Inland Water Transport (Shanghai) Vol. II Jan 1947 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 706/5 CNRRA (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - CNRRA Air Transport Requisition (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - Honululu (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - Crew Contracts (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039 Procument (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/9 Surprop Jan. 1946 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/9 Surprop (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 239/9 Surrop (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 035 Transportation (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 035/6 Inland Water Transport Apr. 1946 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - India (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/4 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 239/4 Procurement Vol. I thru Dec. 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 239/4 Procurement Vol. II Jan. 1947 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/4 Procurement Vol. I Oct. 1945-June 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/4 Procurement Vol. II July 1946-September 1947 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/4 Procurement Vol. Ill October 1947 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/7 Surplus Procurement Vol. I October 1945 - June 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/7A Surplus Procurement, India, Trucks & Trailers for Siam (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/7 Surprop (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - New Zealand (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/3 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 293/3 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - Procurement, Jan. 1946 - Dec. 1947 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippine Islands (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/8 Surprop Oct. 1945 - Mar. 1946 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/8 Surprop Apr. - June 1946 Vol. II (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/8 Surprop July - Dec. 1946 Vol. III (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 039/8 Surprop Jan. 1947 Vol. IV (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - 239/8A Surprop Policy Vol. I thru Dec. 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippine Islands (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/8A Surprop Policy Vol. II Jan. 1947 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/8B Procurement Surprop Vol. I thru Dec. 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/8B Procurement Surprop Vol. II Jan. 1947 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 039/8 Surprop (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 035 Transportation (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 035/6 Philippine Inland Water Transportation Jan. 1946 Vol. I Manila (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 036 Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - SWPAO (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 036/11 Fisheries (Sydney Vol. I) (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/2 Procurement Vol. I thru Dec. 1945 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/2 Procurement Vol. II Jan. 1946 - May 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/2 Procurement Vol. Ill June 1946 - 3uly 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/2 Procurement Vol. IV Aug. 1946 - Dec. 1946 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/2 Procurement Vol. V Jan. 1947 on (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 035 Transportation (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 035/6 Inland Water Transportation Jan. 1946 Vol. I Sydney (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - SWPAO - UNRRA London-Sydney 1946-8 (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - United Kingdom (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 239/11 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 039/12 Procurement (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
    - 039/12 Procurement H.K.E.R.O. Jan. 1947 Vol. I (Box FE/9, Folder Side 2)
- Series VI. Office of the General Counsel
  - Subseries VI.1: Executive Office. Subject File.
    - Ability to Pay (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Cairo Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - H.I.A.S.ter Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Multilateral Agreement on DPs (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Ratification of UNRRA by Member Governments (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Riga Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - SACMED-UNRRA (Supreme Allied Command Mediterranean) (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Wheat Agreement, UNRRA Relation to (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreements (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreements and Contracts (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Executive Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Trade Agreement (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Agricultural Rehabilitation (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - American-Hawaiian Contract etc. (Shipping) (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Antwerp Contract, Termination of (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Appropriation Acts (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - $550,000,000 Appropriation Facts and Fiction 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Appropriation U.S. Bedgetary Tables & Supporting Material (1944) (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Appropriation U.S. Wool and Cotton A,endment (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Appropriations (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Aquilla - P.O.L. (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Arbitration (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Areas, Bureau of (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Areas, Devastated (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Assignment, UNRRA of Responsibilities HQ (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Authority, Delegation of (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Authorization, UNRRA 1944 H.J. Res. 192 Congress Vote (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Barter (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Federal Supply, Administrative Expenses of after June 30, 1947 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - CARE (Cooperation for American Remittance to Europe) (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Certificate of Identity (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Charters & Charter Party re Shipping (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Children (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Unaccompanied and Displaced 1944-6 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Unaccompanied and Displaced 1947 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Civil Service (Box GC/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Chronology (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Jan.-Mar. 1944 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Jan.-Mar. 1944 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - April - June 1944 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - July 1944 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - April - August (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - September 1944 - January 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - February - March 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - April 1945 - May 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - June 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - July 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - August 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - September 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - October 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - November 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - December 1945 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - January 1946 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - February 1946 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - March 1946 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - April 1946 (Box GC/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Chronology (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Frederick Chait (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - January - June 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - July - December 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - January - June 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - July - December 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - January - May 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - David Cobb (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - February 26 - May 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - June 3 - August 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Cutler, December 1945 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Davis, February 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Hawes, A.B., July 1944 - May 1945 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Hawes, June 1945 - December 1945 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Huang, Robert T., February 1944 - August 1945 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Lamberton, H.C., Jan. - Dec. 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Lloyd, C., May 1945 - Dec. 1945 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Lloyd, C.T., Oct. 1946 - Dec. 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Lloyd, C.T., Jan. - May 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Lloyd, David D., Dec. 1946 - March 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Morse, W., May 1947 - Feb. 1949 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Reading File (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - June 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - August 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - October 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 1)
    - November 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - December 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - January 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - February 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - March 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - April 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - May 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - June 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - July 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - August 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - September 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - October 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - November 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - December 1948 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - January 1949 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - February 1949 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Chronology (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - May 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - June 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - July 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - August - September 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - October - November 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - December 1946 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - January 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - February 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - March 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - April - June 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)
    - July - October 1947 (Box GC/2, Folder Side 2)